This video will explain the production of zipper pockets.
First is the arrangement of zipper pocket panels.
We can combine the large and small panels.
Then we can show the basic line of the panel.
It is convenient for us to align the position of the pocket panel.
Select the pocket panel.
Click the quick arrangement button in the upper right corner of the positioning ball.
You can arrange the panel on our large panel.
Use the blue arrow of the positioning ball.
Do not loosen the left and right keys.
Drag the mouse down.
Then you can move the panel out.
When we move to the edge of the panel, the shadow appears, and it can be stopped.
At this time, our pocket panel will be on our large panel.
Next, we will arrange.
You can select the large panel and the pocket panel at the same time.
As an overall arrangement, open the arrangement point of the virtual model.
Then select the panel and click the left button on the corresponding arrangement point.
You can complete the overall arrangement of our large and pocket panels.
The rest of the panels are also arranged according to the structure.
After the arrangement, we can deal with the panel and the pocket panels.
First, select the collet outline tool.
Then select the base line on the pocket panel.
Click the return car to collet.
Then select the free sewing tool.
Sew the pocket.
Next, continue to select the collet outline tool.
Collet the zipper pattern.
Click the return car to collet.
Then select the adjustment panel tool.
Click the right button on the internal pattern.
Choose to convert to move.
The rest of the parts are sewed and made according to the normal structure of the part.
This is an effect that we sewed and completed the simulation.
Next, we will make the collet outline.
To make it easier for us to check, we can close the basic line display.
Let us see the effect of the pocket.
Next, select the collet outline tool.
The addition of the collet can be added in the 3D window.
You can also add it in the 2D window.
First, let's explain the addition of the 3D window.
Click the left button to start.
Then we follow the line of adding the zipper.
Slide the mouse to the bottom.
Click the left double click to end.
Next, make the zipper on the other side.
Click the same button to start.
Then double click to end.
This completes the addition of the zipper.
Next, let's talk about how to add the zipper on the 2D version.
Move the mouse to the 2D version.
Click the start button.
Double click to end.
This is also the start button.
Then you can complete the addition of the zipper.
After adding the zipper, you can make some settings to the zipper parameters.
We select the move tool.
Then select the zipper.
In the property editor, we can edit the length of the zipper.
Then you can also edit the size of the zipper.
Here you can select the number of zipper.
Then at the bottom, you can edit the total width of the zipper.
That is, its width of the zipper.
Here is 1.2 cm.
After editing the number, let's simulate it.
You can see that the zipper will simulate
the width of the zipper at the bottom,
and it just fits well on the zipper.
Then we can make some small changes.
Next, we can sew the zipper's two ends.
After making the zipper,
the handle of the zipper is on the two ends,
and the zipper does not match with the button.
So here we have a hole here.
For convenience,
we can change the rendering type of the clothing to the texture of the surface.
Let's move the zipper to the bottom.
Then we are at the bottom of the chain
Drag our board
Here you can see
It is actually an opening state
Close the simulation while dragging the board
Then you can use the line sewing tool to sew
Use a pair of more sewing tools here
Click on the board first
Then press the Shift key not to loosen
Then click on the chain on one side
Click on the other side again
When clicking
Please pay attention to the position and direction of the seam line
Finally, release the Shift key
Complete our sewing
Simulate
So our chain end is sewn together
And when pulling again
Will not open
When we encounter the two ends of the chain
Less fabric
For example, like the upper end now
Then drag this chain and you will find
It is more difficult to make a gap
This is not convenient to sew
At this time we can select the chain
Then in the attribute editor
Find the option to sew the chain
Turn it off
Then simulate again
At this time the chain will be untied
Then just turn here lightly
You can see
The fabric of the pocket
And the fabric on both sides of our chain are separated
At this time select the sewing tool in the middle line
Click on the fabric of the pocket
Then press the Shift key
Click on the zipper on both sides
Pay attention to the position and direction of the click
Then press the control button again
For simulation
Complete the seam
After the zipper is done
You can adjust some appearance details to it
First select our zipper again
Open the zipper option again
Then select its opening
Change it to a closed opening
If the zipper is not in the opening
Select the opening in the 3D window
Right-click to hide the opening
Below is the setting of the zipper type
Select the zipper
Then click on the top to preset
You can switch to different zipper types
Under the zipper
You can adjust your wrong way
From the other side
You can also set the zipper to the lower edge
And select many zipper types
We also use the supporting parts
To support the zipper
To find the right fit
And accordingly
Then you have the option to refer
You can also choose every stucco
From the top of the zipper
Or chose the middle one
Then you can select the bottom
follow the zipper
Right side
Then click on the shy
Then click on right killed
以上就是关于我们拉链口袋的制作说明,希望能帮助到大家。